<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="aim">Every thought which is repeatedly passed on to the subconscious mind is,
        finally, accepted and acted on. The subconscious mind proceeds to translate that impulse into
        its physical equivalent by the most practical procedure available.\n\nAll thoughts which have been emotionalized and mixed with faith, begin immediately to
        translate themselves into their physical equivalent.\n\nConduct yourself as you would if you were already in the position which you are demanding.
        Practice makes perfect.\n\nFaith is the external elixir that gives life, power and action to the impulse of thought!
        \n\nI know I have the ability to achieve the object of my definite purpose in
        life.\n\nTherefore, I demand of myself persistent, continuous action toward its attainment,
        and I here and now promise to render such action.\n\nI realize the dominating thoughts of my mind will eventually reproduce
        themselves in outward, physical action, and gradually transform themselves into physical reality.
        \n\nTherefore, I will concentrate my thoughts for 30 minutes daily, upon the task of thinking
        of the person I intend to become, thereby creating in my mind a clear mental picture of that person.
        \n\nI know through the principle of auto-suggestion, any desire that I
        persistently hold in my mind will eventually seek expression through some practical means of
        attaining the object back of it.\n\nTherefore, I will devote 10 minutes daily to demanding of
        myself the development of self-confidence.\n\nI have clearly written down a description of my definite chief aim in life.
        \n\nI will never stop trying, until I shall have developed sufficient self-confidence for its attainment.
        \n\nI fully realize that no wealth or position can long endure, unless built
        upon truth and justice, therefore, I will engage in no transaction which does not benefit
        all it affects.\n\nI will induce others to serve me, because of my willingness to serve others.
        \n\nI will eliminate hatred, envy, jealousy, selfishness, and cynism, by developing love for all
        humanity, because a negative attitude toward others can never bring me success.\n\nI will cause
        others to believe in me, because I will believe in them, and in myself.
        \n\nI will sign my name to formula, commit to memory, and repeat it aloud once
        a day, with full faith that it will gradually influence my thoughts and actions so that I
        will become a self-reliant, and successful person.</string>

</resources>