<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="pose_protective">Placing your hands on your face or neck is a low power pose that
        communicates a need for protection from other people.\n\n
    When people cross their legs, they signal that they are really resistant and unreceptive. It can
        be great if you want to distance yourself from someone, but if you are negotiating a great
        deal on a new car you want to buy or if you’re trying to convince your boss for a new raise,
        displaying resistance is not a good idea! Instead, uncross your legs and be open with your
        posture. After all, we all love getting a great deal!\n\n
    Just as crossing your legs can be a bad body language position to take, so can crossing your
        arms. Crossing your arms signals defensiveness and skepticism. When you cross your arms you
        distance yourself from whoever you are speaking with. Instead, uncross your arms next time
        you are trying to connect with someone you’ve just met and you’ll notice it’s easier to
        build a rapport with them.</string>

    <string name="pose_tall_proud">The power pose is the extension of your arms up and over your head as high as possible. It
        creates a V-shape over your head. Lift your chin. This pose actually has been studied and
        documented to increase testosterone, confidence, and leadership qualities in all who make it.
        Next time you’re feeling nervous or unsure of yourself before a big meeting, raise up those arms of
        yours and strike a power pose for two minutes! You’ll be happy you did.\n\n
        When you lift your chin up, you display a great amount of pride, confidence, and dominance.
        If you’ve ever seen someone with their head down, you’ll understand the importance of lifting
        it up! By keeping it up you show you’re content with yourself and secure in who you are. Next
        time you want to display confidence, such as on-stage making a speech, telling a story to a
        group of friends, or interviewing for a desired position, keep your chin up!</string>

    <string name="superwoman">The superwoman pose of standing tall with your hands on your hip offers
        you confidence and signals purpose and energy. In situations where you know you will be
        intimidated and be pushed to nervousness you can try the superwoman pose to put you in control.
        The superwoman pose may not be ideal in certain situations, but it benefits you to take up
        space and take advantage of the room. That can take you from
        looking meek to seeming assertive.\n\nAlways stand or sit up straight. Show your chest. Take space.
        Allow your fingertips to meet your other fingertips to signal authority and power.
        Successful people like Oprah Winfrey and Donald Trump practice this body gesture.\n\n
        The pose of opening your arm at belly level signals that you are willing to expose your
        front and open your arms to win trust. Opening your arm shows that there is no predator in
        the room and you are ready to accommodate the other person. You also stand out and become
        significant in the room because you are noticed with this pose.\n\n
        Leaning towards the other person is a signal of empathy, warmth and likeability. Lean
        towards the other person in a pose and maintain good eye contact to generate openness and
        affection that you do understand whatever they are going through. This is a leadership
        position of compassion and understanding.\n\n
        When you tilt your head forward you show that you are humble and respectful. It shows you
        are honored by the other person and you are not concerned about a difference in status
        between you and the other person. This pose is a gesture that you are signaled to welcome
        and you’re happy to meet someone, even when you have not met the person. It makes the person
        relaxed and less defensive.\n\n

    </string>

    <string name="quote1">"&quot;I think the things you regret most in life are the things you didn’t do.&quot;"</string>
</resources>